let quiz=[
    {
        question: "Which of the following elements was unknown to ancient civilizations :",
      option: [
           "Tin",
           "Aluminium",
           "Mercury",
           "Sulfur",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Plants get their nitrogen from :",
      option: [
           "Rain",
           "Soil",
           "Air",
           "Bedrock",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The half life of tritium is about :",
      option: [
           "3,500 years",
           "40 years",
           "12.3 years",
           "3.7 years",
      ],
       answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What power cycle is used in jet engines :",
      option: [
           "Stirling",
           "Rankine",
           "Otto",
           "Brayton",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What range of frequencies are usually referred to as the UHF Band :",
      option: [
           "3 to 30 Megahertz",
           "30 to 300 Megahertz",
           "300 to 3,000 Megahertz",
           "30,000 to 3,00,000 Megahertz",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What range of frequencies are usually reffered to as audio frequencies for humans",
      option: [
           "0 to 20 hertz",
           "20 to 20,000 hertz",
           "200 to 2,00,000 hertz",
           "10,000 to 30,000 hertz",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The study of poisons is called :",
      option: [
           "Oncology",
           "Toxicology",
           "Phrenology",
           "Ergonomics",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following materials is used along with iron core and limestone to produce iron in a modern blast furnace :",
      option: [
           "Coke",
           "Cementite",
           "Coal",
           "Bauxite",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "The first American Astronaut to ORBIT the Earth was :",
      option: [
           "Alan Shepard",
           "John Glenn",
           "Gus Grissom",
           "Scott Carpenter",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The launch of the first LIQUID fueled rocket in the world is attributed to :",
      option: [
           "China",
           "Russia",
           "United States",
           "Germany",
      ],
      answer: 3 ,
    },
]   